- ConversationTopicId: 0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument
  PlayerPrompt: "@0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_PlayForTown
  PlayerPrompt: "@0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0403a_Huntsman_TaskTopic_DeliverPotions
  PlayerPrompt: "@04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_TalkTo_Odnell_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_TalkTo_Odnell_next_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument
  PlayerPrompt: "@0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ChooseInstrument_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_PlayForTown
  PlayerPrompt: "@0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0440a_00_AtticusDelphi_TaskTopic_DeliverPotions
  PlayerPrompt: "@04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_TalkTo_Atticus_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_TalkTo_Atticus_next_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0410_Barkeep_TaskTopic_PlayForTown
  PlayerPrompt: "@0410_Barkeep_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0410_Barkeep_TaskTopic_PlayForTown_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0410a_Barkeep_TaskTopic_SaveBar
  PlayerPrompt: "@0410a_Barkeep_TaskTopic_SaveBar_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0410a_Barkeep_TaskTopic_SaveBar_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience
  PlayerPrompt: "@0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_02
  PlayerPrompt: "@0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_02_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0441a_SairaYangandul_TaskTopic_EarnAudience_02_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron
  PlayerPrompt: "@0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02
  PlayerPrompt: "@0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0442a_ConcettaSacco_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0432a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron
  PlayerPrompt: "@0443a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0443a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0432a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02
  PlayerPrompt: "@0443a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0443a_OuShen_TaskTopic_EarnPatron_02_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0450a_TownGuard_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_02_02a_TownGuard_Prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_02a_TownGuard_Response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ
  PlayerPrompt: "@0404a_Constable_Comment_Rumors_c_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@0404a_Constable_Comment_Rumors_c_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0440a_Atticus_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_02_02c_Atticus_Prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_02c_Atticus_Response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0403a_Huntsman_TaskTopic_AskAboutAdiana
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_04_2a_Huntsman_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_04_2a_Huntsman_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0405a_Artificer_TaskTopic_AskAboutAdiana
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_04_2b_Artificer_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_04_2b_Artificer_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0402a_Magistrate_TaskTopic_ReturnStaff
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_12_02a_Magistrate_ReturnStaff_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_12_02a_Magistrate_ReturnStaff_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0404a_Constable_TaskTopic_ReturnStaff
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_12_02c_Constable_ReturnStaff_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_12_02c_Constable_ReturnStaff_Response_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0404a_Constable_Comment_UseStaff
  PlayerPrompt: "@0404a_Constable_Comment_UseStaff_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0404a_Constable_Comment_UseStaff_b"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99A_MSQ_07_TalkToAnthuras
  PlayerPrompt: "@Anthurus_01_Comment_Rescue_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@Anthurus_01_Comment_Rescue_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0441a_Saira_TaskTopic_RumorsMSQ
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_02_02b_Saira_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_02b_Saira_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
